

Yurii Kitsera

Contacts

Address

Ukraine, Lviv

Phone

+380678656486

Email

y.kitsera@gmail.com

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuriy-kitsera-2a896b115/

github

https://github.com/YraKot

Professional Summary

1.5+ year experience as a Front-End dev. I am interested in Angular 2+ and I'm using it in my pet project.

Looking for a job that will help me improve my skills. Responsible, diligent, reliable, able to listen, friendly, able to learn quickly and team player.

Work Experience

Chunkup, Web Development Lab

04.2019 - now

https://qa.prorfx.com/

UPQODE LLC, front-end dev position.

01.2018 - 04.2019

- https://www.accenture.com/us-en
- http://test.viewdemo.co/wp/digitank/
- http://test.viewdemo.co/wp/iup/
- https://dragonboat.io
- https://zinc.co/
- http://dev.viewdemo.co/html/skil-tools/
- http://dev.viewdemo.co/html/ego/
- http://dev.viewdemo.co/wp/chase/

Freelance web developer

06.2017 - 09.2017

09.2016 - 01.2017

2006 - 2011

- http://www.proditech.com.ua/
- http://www.ecobot.com.ua/

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Institute of Computer Sciences and Information Technologies, Department of Applied Linguistics, Position: engineer.

Additional Education

EPAM System, The Education program: "Data Warehouse Business Intelligence".

Education

Lviv Polytechnic National University, Institute of Computer Technologies, Automation and Metrology, Specialist degree in Computer System Engineering.

Languages

Ukrainian – native English – intermediate Russian – intermediate

Technical skills

- HTML5, PUG, Nunjucks
- CSS3, SCSS, SASS, LESS
- JS, ES6, TS, jQuery
- Gulp, Webpack, Git
- Phtoshop, Zeplin, Sketch